<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The association on PyBCN - The Barcelona Python Association</title><link>https://pybcn.org/pybcn_association/</link><description>Recent content in The association on PyBCN - The Barcelona Python Association</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://pybcn.org/pybcn_association/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Information</title><link>https://pybcn.org/pybcn_association/information/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pybcn.org/pybcn_association/information/</guid><description>After 10 years of experience organizing python-related events and more than 3000 members on Meetup, Python Barcelona (PyBCN) was officially registered as a non-profit association in 2018. PyBCN is a meeting point for all the Barcelona Python community, and we organize different monthly activities like PyBCN and PyLadiesBCN meetups and practice sessions, along with some annual events like PyDay BCN or PyDataBCN.
Would you like to be a part of PyBCN?</description></item><item><title>How to collaborate</title><link>https://pybcn.org/pybcn_association/collaborate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pybcn.org/pybcn_association/collaborate/</guid><description>My money&amp;rsquo;s in that office, right? If she start giving me some bullshit about it ain&amp;rsquo;t there, and we got to go someplace else and get it, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna shoot you in the head then and there. Then I&amp;rsquo;m gonna shoot that bitch in the kneecaps, find out where my goddamn money is. She gonna tell me too. Hey, look at me when I&amp;rsquo;m talking to you, motherfucker. You listen: we go in there, and that nigga Winston or anybody else is in there, you the first motherfucker to get shot.</description></item><item><title>Become a member!</title><link>https://pybcn.org/pybcn_association/membership/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pybcn.org/pybcn_association/membership/</guid><description>The Python Barcelona Association, a.k.a. PyBCN, is a non-profit organisation with more than 10 years of history, focused on increasing the usage and knowledge of the Python programming language. By becoming a member, you&amp;rsquo;ll support the association&amp;rsquo;s activities and programs, helping us to increase the number of activities, to improve them (i.e. getting a better recording system for the meetups) and to cover basic expenses (domains, meetup fees&amp;hellip;). For just 20€/year you can now become a member of our community!</description></item><item><title>Organize with us</title><link>https://pybcn.org/pybcn_association/organize-with-us/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pybcn.org/pybcn_association/organize-with-us/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Organizers</title><link>https://pybcn.org/pybcn_association/organizers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pybcn.org/pybcn_association/organizers/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Promote your event</title><link>https://pybcn.org/pybcn_association/promote-your-event/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pybcn.org/pybcn_association/promote-your-event/</guid><description>Conditions: The event must be related to Python. It must be free, or offer some advantages to PyBCN members. It must be hosted in Spain, or be accessible remotely. There must be a Code of conduct in line with our own. It must be clearly stated who is organizing the event, and therefore who is responsible for it. What do you get We&amp;rsquo;ll forward your event information to our PyBCN meetup list, with more than 3K members.</description></item><item><title>Sponsor us</title><link>https://pybcn.org/pybcn_association/sponsor-us/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pybcn.org/pybcn_association/sponsor-us/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Code of Conduct</title><link>https://pybcn.org/pybcn_association/coc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pybcn.org/pybcn_association/coc/</guid><description>PyBCN is dedicated to providing a respectful, harassment-free community for everyone. We do not tolerate harassment or bullying of any community member in any form. This does not only extend to members to local PyBCN communities, but to anyone who chooses to become involved in the larger PyBCN community of users, developers and integrators through events or interactions.
Harassment includes offensive verbal/electronic comments related to personal characteristics or choices, sexual images or comments in public or online spaces, deliberate intimidation, bullying, stalking, following, harassing photography or recording, sustained disruption of talks, IRC chats, electronic meetings, physical meetings or other events, inappropriate physical contact, or unwelcome sexual attention.</description></item><item><title>Propose a talk</title><link>https://pybcn.org/pybcn_association/propose-a-talk/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pybcn.org/pybcn_association/propose-a-talk/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Job offers</title><link>https://pybcn.org/pybcn_association/job-offers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pybcn.org/pybcn_association/job-offers/</guid><description>All job offers are sent to the subscribers of the mailing list.
To check past job offers, go to the Mailing List Archive.
To publish a new job offer:
Send it to pybcn+jobs at googlegroups.com. Subject: Job offer: {POSITION} at {COMPANY}, where {POSITION} is the position of the job offer, and {COMPANY} is the name of your company. For the body, feel free to check other job offers as inspiration.</description></item><item><title>Become a member!</title><link>https://pybcn.org/pybcn_association/membership-cancel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pybcn.org/pybcn_association/membership-cancel/</guid><description>As a member, you can: Have a voice and vote in our general assemblies, Participate in our board elections, Receive information about the activities of the association, Become part of the working groups, Ask questions about the association management, Make use of the common services that the association establishes or has at your disposal, Be heard before the adoption of disciplinary measures, Participate in the government and the management of the association, its services and activities, Have a copy of the statutes, and Consult the association's books.</description></item><item><title>Thanks for becoming a member!</title><link>https://pybcn.org/pybcn_association/membership-thanks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pybcn.org/pybcn_association/membership-thanks/</guid><description>As a member, you can: Have a voice and vote in our general assemblies, Participate in our board elections, Receive information about the activities of the association, Become part of the working groups, Ask questions about the association management, Make use of the common services that the association establishes or has at your disposal, Be heard before the adoption of disciplinary measures, Participate in the government and the management of the association, its services and activities, Have a copy of the statutes, and Consult the association's books.</description></item></channel></rss>