<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>PyDay BCN on PyBCN - The Barcelona Python Association</title><link>https://pybcn.org/events/pyday_bcn/</link><description>Recent content in PyDay BCN on PyBCN - The Barcelona Python Association</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://pybcn.org/events/pyday_bcn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>PyDay BCN 2024</title><link>https://pybcn.org/events/pyday_bcn/pyday_bcn_2024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pybcn.org/events/pyday_bcn/pyday_bcn_2024/</guid><description>About PyDay BCN 2024 We are excited to announce the 8th edition of PyDay in Barcelona!
PyDay is an event packed with FREE python-related workshops and activities for the Python community. It is organized once per year. Over the last seven editions, PyDay has become a fantastic opportunity to share our love for Python and engage users, companies, and newcomers!
When and where It is scheduled for Saturday 9th November at Canòdrom, from 9:00 a.</description></item><item><title>PyDay BCN 2023</title><link>https://pybcn.org/events/pyday_bcn/pyday_bcn_2023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pybcn.org/events/pyday_bcn/pyday_bcn_2023/</guid><description>About PyDay BCN 2023 We are organizing the the seventh edition of PyDay in Barcelona!
PyDay is an event full of FREE python-related workshops and activities for the Python community, organized once per year. Over the last six editions, PyDay has become a great opportunity to share our love for Python and engage users, companies and newcomers into it!
When and where It is scheduled for Saturday 11th November in Universitat de Barcelona, from 9:00am to 18:00pm CET, aprox.</description></item><item><title>PyDay BCN 2022</title><link>https://pybcn.org/events/pyday_bcn/pyday_bcn_2022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pybcn.org/events/pyday_bcn/pyday_bcn_2022/</guid><description>About PyDay BCN 2022 We are organizing the the sixth edition of PyDay in Barcelona!
PyDay is an event full of FREE python-related workshops and activities for the Python community, organized once per year. Over the last five editions, PyDay has become a great opportunity to share our love for Python and engage users, companies and newcomers into it!
When and where It is scheduled for Saturday 26th November in Canòdrom - Ateneu d&amp;rsquo;Innovació Digital i Democràtica, from 9:30pm to 19:00pm CET, aprox.</description></item><item><title>PyDay BCN 2021</title><link>https://pybcn.org/events/pyday_bcn/pyday_bcn_2021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pybcn.org/events/pyday_bcn/pyday_bcn_2021/</guid><description>About PyDay BCN 2021 We are organizing the the fifth edition of PyDay in Barcelona!
PyDay is an event full of FREE python-related workshops and activities for the Python community, organized once per year. Over the last four editions, PyDay has become a great opportunity to share our love for Python and engage users, companies and newcomers into it!
When and where It is scheduled for Saturday 27th November in Canòdrom - Ateneu d&amp;rsquo;Innovació Digital i Democràtica, from 9:30pm to 19:00pm CET, aprox.</description></item><item><title>PyDay BCN 2020</title><link>https://pybcn.org/events/pyday_bcn/pyday_bcn_2020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pybcn.org/events/pyday_bcn/pyday_bcn_2020/</guid><description>What is PyDay BCN 2020 about? We are excited to announce that we are organizing the fourth edition of PyDay in Barcelona! This year it will be an online event with up to 200 attendees. It is scheduled for 12th of December from 4:00pm to 8:45pm CET.
PyDay is an event full of FREE python-related activities for the Python community, organized once per year. Over the last three editions, PyDay has become a great opportunity to share our love for Python and engage users, companies and newcomers into it!</description></item><item><title>PyDay BCN 2019</title><link>https://pybcn.org/events/pyday_bcn/pyday_bcn_2019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pybcn.org/events/pyday_bcn/pyday_bcn_2019/</guid><description>This event has ended! You can see some photos here.
Archived content We are excited to announce that we are organizing the third edition of PyDay in Barcelona!
PyDay Barcelona 2019 is going to take place on November 16th fgin Universitat de Barcelona, a full day full of FREE python-related activities for the Python community. Over the last two editions, PyDay has become a great opportunity to share our love for Python and engage users, companies and newcomers into it!</description></item><item><title>PyDay BCN 2018</title><link>https://pybcn.org/events/pyday_bcn/pyday_bcn_2018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pybcn.org/events/pyday_bcn/pyday_bcn_2018/</guid><description>We are excited and glad to announce that we are organizing the second edition of PyDay in Barcelona! PyDay Barcelona 2018 is going to take place on November 24th at PuntMultimèdia (Espanya Industrial, Sants), full of FREE workshops, talks and contests for the local Python community and an opportunity to spread the word of its existence to other people that could be interested in Python. What is PyDay Barcelona 2018 about?</description></item><item><title>PyDay BCN 2016</title><link>https://pybcn.org/events/pyday_bcn/pyday_bcn_2016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pybcn.org/events/pyday_bcn/pyday_bcn_2016/</guid><description>We are excited and glad to announce that we are organizing our first big event related to Python. PyDay BCN 2016 is going to take place in Barcelona on 15 and 17 September: two days of FREE different and funny activities about Python.
We count with an incredible group of volunteers, sponsors, and contributing entities and companies. Thanks to all them.
We really hope you'll have a great time attending to these!</description></item></channel></rss>